<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<config>
<!-- 
################################################################################
## Rig Client Configuration Descriptions.                                     ##
################################################################################

Each property should be configured with the following attributes:

  * name      - Name of the configuration property
  * stanza    - Property groupings
  * mandatory - Whether the property is mandatory or optional, if the value is
                'yes', 'true' or 'on' the property is mandatory
  * type      - The data type of the property value, this can be either 'STRING',
                'INTEGER', 'FLOAT', 'BOOLEAN' or 'CHAR'.
  * format    - Configuration format expected
  * default   - Default format 
  * restart   - Whether the value will be applied immediately or on next rig client
                start
  * example   - Example value
-->

<!-- 
################################################################################
## File: rigclient.properties                                                 ##
################################################################################
-->
<!-- ##### Rig properties ################################################ -->
<property name="Rig_Name" 
		  stanza="Rig" 
		  mandatory="yes" 
		  type="STRING" 
		  restart="yes"
 		  example="Rig_1"
 		  format="&lt;String&gt;" 
 		  default="">
Uniquely identifies a rig within the remote laboratory.
</property>

<property name="Rig_Type" 
		  stanza="Rig" 
		  mandatory="yes"
		  type="STRING" 
		  restart="yes"
 		  example="Inclined_Plane" 
 		  format="&lt;String&gt;" 
 		  default="">
Identifies the rig as an identical configuration of same software and hardware.
This means any rig in this type can be used in place of any other rig in the same
type.
</property>

<property name="Rig_Capabilities" 
		  stanza="Rig" 
 		  mandatory="yes" 
 		  type="STRING" 
 		  restart="yes"
 		  example="tag1,tag2,tag3" 
 		  format="&lt;String&gt;,...,&lt;String&gt;" 
 		  default="">
A list of identifying tags which may be used to correlate rigs into collections
to queue or book for. This allows, for example, multiple rig types to be 
collectively queued to get the first free rig in any of the rig types.
</property>

<property name="Rig_Class" 
		  stanza="Rig" 
		  mandatory="yes" 
		  type="STRING" 
		  restart="yes"
 		  example="" 
 		  format="[au.edu.uts.eng.remotelabs.rig.ConfiguredRig] | [au.edu.uts.eng.remotelabs.rig.ConfiguredControlledRig] | &lt;String&gt;"
 		  default="">
<![CDATA[
The fully qualified class name of the Rig Clients rig type class. This must 
implement the interface 'IRig' but in practice most likely extends the 
abstract class 'AbstractRig'. Two generic implementations exist that provide
the required rig type class functionality. These are: 
<ul>
    <li><strong>ConfiguredRig</strong> - Class
    which is configured with the name of 'action' classes (classes 
    implementing interfaces that are run at certain session events);</li>
     <li><strong>ConfiguredControlledRig</strong> - 
     Similar class to the former but also implements the option rig client
     control interface;</li> 
</ul>
All the above classes are located in the package 
'au.edu.uts.eng.remotelabs.rigclient.rig' which must be prefixed to the 
above class names to make a fully qualified class name.
<br />
Consult the 'Sahara Development Handbook' for further detail about rig type 
classes and how to create them.
]]>
</property>

<property name="Rig_Client_IP_Address"
          stanza="Rig"
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="138.25.49.151" 
		  format="&lt;IP&gt;|&lt;hostname&gt;|empty"
		  default="">
The IP address of the machine the Rig Client is running on. This is needed if 
the Rig Client machine has multiple network interfaces and you want to ensure 
the external IP address is transmitted as the communication address. If left 
empty, the address of the first iterated network device is used.
</property>

<property name="Listening_Network_Interface"
          stanza="Rig"
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="eth0" 
		  format="&lt;String&gt;|empty"
		  default="">
The name of the network interface of the Rig CIlient is listening on. This is
needed if the Rig Client machine has multiple network interfaces and you want
a specific network interface to be used. This may be used in preference to
the 'Rig_Client_IP_Address' property as it allows a specific network interface
to be used while still detecting the IP address at runtime (i.e. Supports DHCP).	
</property>	

<property name="Listening_Port"
          stanza="Rig"
          mandatory="yes" 
          type="INTEGER" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="8080" 
		  format="&lt;int&gt;"
		  default=""> 
The port number the Rig Client server is to listen on. This must be externally 
accessible by the Scheduling Server.		  
</property>

<!-- #### Scheduling Server properties ######################################## -->
<property name="Scheduling_Server_Address" 
          stanza="Scheduling Server"
          mandatory="yes" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="localhost" 
		  format="&lt;String&gt;" 
		  default="">
The address of the Scheduling Server. This can be the host name or the IP 
address of the computer the Scheduling Server is running on.
</property>

<property name="Scheduling_Server_Port"
          stanza="Scheduling Server"
          mandatory="yes" 
          type="INTEGER" 
          example="8080" 
          restart="yes"
		  format="&lt;int&gt;" 
		  default="">
The port number the Scheduling Server is listening on.
</property>

<property name="Scheduling_Server_Update_Period" 
		  stanza="Scheduling Server" 
		  mandatory="no" 
		  type="INTEGER" 
		  restart="yes"
		  example="30" 
		  format="&lt;30&gt;" 
		  default="30">
The time in seconds between sending status updates from the Rig Client to the
Scheduling Server.
</property>

<!-- #### Miscellaneous Properties ######################################## -->
<property name="Concurrent_Requests" 
		  stanza="Miscellaneous" 
		  mandatory="no" 
		  type="INTEGER" 
		  restart="yes"
		  example="10" 
		  format="&lt;int&gt;" 
		  default="50">
The number of concurrent requests the Rig Client can service. If there are more than
this number of requests, the extra requests are queued.
</property>

<property name="Action_Failure_Threshold" 
      	  stanza="Miscellaneous"
      	  mandatory="no" 
      	  type="INTEGER" 
      	  restart="yes"
		  example="3" 
		  format="&lt;int&gt;" 
		  default="3">
The threshold indicating how many times an action can fail before the rig is put
off line.
</property>

<property name="Test_Light_Time"
      	  stanza="Miscellaneous"
      	  mandatory="no" 
      	  type="STRING" 
      	  restart="yes"
		  example="07:00" 
		  format="&lt;hour of day&gt;:&lt;minute&gt;" 
		  default="09:00">
The time at which the laboratory 'light' time starts. The light time is when the
test frequency is set to be specified test run interval for tests which enable
light-dark scheduling. The time should be configured in 24 hour time with a
column ':' between the hours and minute portions. The default light time is 09:00.		  
</property>

<property name="Test_Dark_Time"
      	  stanza="Miscellaneous"
      	  mandatory="no" 
      	  type="STRING" 
      	  restart="yes"
		  example="20:00" 
		  format="&lt;hour of day&gt;:&lt;minute&gt;" 
		  default="18:00">
The time at which the laboratory 'dark' time starts. The dark time is when the 
test frequency is set to the specified test run interval multiplied by the 
specified dark time factor for exerciser tests which enable light-dark exerciser 
scheduling. It is the test which specifies the dark time factor. The time should 
be configured with 24 hour time with a column ':' between the hours and minutes 
portions. The default dark time is 18:00.
</property>

<!-- 
################################################################################
## File: configuredrig.properties                                             ##
################################################################################
-->
<property name="Action_Package_Prefixes" 
          stanza="Configured Rig" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="au.edu.labshare.rigclient.action; au.edu.remotelabs.rigclient"
		  format="&lt;Package&gt;;...;&lt;Package&gt;"
		  default="">
<![CDATA[
The list of package names that are used in action class resolution. Class 
resolution works using the following algorithm:
<ol>
	<li>The configured controller class name is assumed to be a fully
    qualified class name and an attempt is made to load it. If it 
    is found then that class is used;</li>
    <li>The configured action class name is appended to the first configured
    action package prefix and an attempt is made to load it. If it is found 
    then that class is used;</li>
    <li>The configured action class name is appended to the next configured 
    action package prefix and an attempt is made to load it. If it is found 
    then that class is used. This occurs until either the class is found or
    all the configured action package prefixes are tried;</li> 
</ol>
Multiple action package prefixes can be configured using the ';' character
as the delimiter between packages.
]]>
</property>

<property name="Access_Actions" 
          stanza="Configured Rig" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="access.RdpAccessAction"
		  format="&lt;Class&gt;;...;&lt;Class&gt;"
		  default="">
Access actions assign access and revoke access to and from the assigned master
user and run at the beginning and end of sessions. This configures the list 
of access actions to use. Multiple access actions can be configured, separating 
each with a ';' character. When multiple access actions are configured, the 
assignment methods are invoked in order they are configured and the revocation 
methods are invoked in reverse order they are configured.
</property>

<property name="Slave_Access_Actions" 
          stanza="Configured Rig" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="slave.VncSlaveAccessAction"
		  format="&lt;Class&gt;;...;&lt;Class&gt;"
		  default="">
Slave access actions assign and revoke access for secondary session users.
This configures the list of slave access actions to load. Multiple slave access 
actions can be configured, separating each with a ';' character.When multiple 
slave access actions are configured, the slave assignment methods are 
invoked in the order they are configured and the slave revocation methods are 
invoked in the reverse order they are configured.
</property>

<property name="Notify_Actions" 
          stanza="Configured Rig" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="notify.TSNotifyAction"
		  format="&lt;Class&gt;;...;&lt;Class&gt;"
		  default="">
Notify actions provide notifications to users of session event messages and are
useful if the users focus may not be on the web interface. For example providing
a Windows popup when a users focus is on using Remote Desktop.  This configures
the list of notification actions to load. Multiple notification actions can be
configured, separating each with a ';' character.
</property>

<property name="Detection_Actions" 
          stanza="Configured Rig" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="detect.WTSDetectionAction"
		  format="&lt;Class&gt;;...;&lt;Class&gt;"
		  default="">
Detection actions are used to verify a user is actually using a rig when in 
session. If they are not, they are removed from the rig after a permission
configured timeout period. This configures the list of detection actions to 
load. Multiple detection actions can be configured, separating each 
with a ';' character.
</property>

<property name="Reset_Actions" 
          stanza="Configured Rig" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="reset.PowerResetAction"
		  format="&lt;Class&gt;;...;&lt;Class&gt;"
		  default="">
Reset actions are run at the end of sessions to cleanup the rig to be ready
for the next user. This configures the list of reset actions to load. Multiple
reset actions can be configured, separating each with a ';' character.
</property>

<property name="Test_Actions" 
          stanza="Configured Rig" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="test.PingTestAction"
		  format="&lt;Class&gt;;...;&lt;Class&gt;"
		  default="">
Test actions are used to ensure the rig is ready for use by running tests
on the system when it is free. These tests report the rig status and if 
one of the tests fail, the rig is taken offline. This configures the list
of test actions to load. Multiple test actions can be configured, separating
each with a ';' character.
</property>

<!-- #### Administrative Interface ############################################ -->
<property name="Admin_Username" 
		  stanza="Admin" 
		  mandatory="no" 
		  type="STRING" 
		  restart="no"
		  example="admin" 
		  format="&lt;String&gt;" 
		  default="admin">
The username to login to the administrative web interface. If this is not 
configured the default username is 'admin'.
</property>

<property name="Admin_Password" 
          stanza="Admin" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="no"
		  example="adminpasswd"
		  format="&lt;String&gt;"
		  default="passwd">
The password to login to the administrative web interface. If this is not
configured the defaul password is 'passwd'.
</property>

<!-- 
################################################################################
## File: logger.properties                                                    ##
################################################################################
-->
<property name="Logger_Type" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="yes" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="SystenErr"
		  format="[SystemErr|File|RolledFile|Syslog|WinEvents]"
		  default="">
<![CDATA[
The logging subsystem which specifies where logs are persisted to. The following 
logging types are implemented: 
<ul>
	<li><strong>SystemErr</strong> - logs messages to the process standard 
	error stream;</li>
	<li><strong>File</strong> - logs messages to a plain text file and is 
	susceptible to log file bloat;</li>
	<li><strong>RolledFile</strong> - logs messages to a plain text file 
	and is rolled when it reaches a configured size;</li>
	<li><strong>Syslog</strong> - logs messages to a Syslog server; </li>
	<li><strong>WinEvents</strong> - logs messages to the Windows Event 
	Log.</li>
</ul>
NOTE: The WinEvents logger only runs on Windows and requires the file 
'NTEventLogAppender.dll' to placed in PATH.
]]>
</property>

<property name="Log_Level" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="yes" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="INFO"
		  format="[ERROR|WARN|INFO|DEBUG]"
		  default="">
<![CDATA[
The level of log messages that are logged. Configuring a more verbose log 
level will print that log levels messages and the preceding less verbose log
levels. The log levels that may be configured in order of least verbosity are:
<ul>
	<li><strong>ERROR</strong> - Messages that are generated by events that cause unexpected 
	results and stop the expected program execution sequence; </li>
	<li><strong>WARN</strong> - Messages that are generated by events that cause undesired 
	results but do not stop the expected program execution sequence; </li>
	<li><strong>INFO</strong> - Message that generated by events that are regular in occurrence, 
	however are useful in audit trails; </li>
	<li><strong>DEBUG</strong> - Messages specifying program execution and progression.</li>
]]>
</property>

<property name="Log_File_Name" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="rigclient.log"
		  format="&lt;String&gt;"
		  default="">
The name of the text file the 'File' and 'RolledFile' loggers log to.
</property>

<property name="Log_File_Max_Size" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="INTEGER" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="3"
		  format="&lt;int&gt;"
		  default="10">
Maximum file size for the rolled logger log file in megabytes.
</property>

<property name="Log_File_Backups" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="INTEGER" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="5"
		  format="&lt;int&gt;"
		  default="5">
Maximum number of backups for the rolled file logger log file backups. 
After the maximum number of backups is exceeded, the oldest log backup file 
is deleted.
</property>

<property name="Syslog_Host" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="127.0.0.1"
		  format="&lt;hostname&gt;"
		  default="">
The host name of IP of the Syslog server.
</property>

<property name="Syslog_Local_Facility_Num" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="INTEGER" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="4"
		  format="&lt;int&gt;"
		  default="">
Syslog log local facility number to use (between 1 to 7). 
</property>

<property name="Default_Log_Format" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="[__LEVEL__] - [__ISO8601__] - __MESSAGE__"
		  format="&lt;Format String&gt;"
		  default="[__LEVEL__] - [__ISO8601__] - __MESSAGE__">
<![CDATA[
The format of the log messages can be specifying by providing a format 
string with macros which are be replaced by their actual values. 
The following is a list of macros that may be put in format strings:  
<ul>
	<li><strong>__MESSAGE__</strong> - Actual message; </li>
    <li><strong>__LEVEL__</strong> - Logging level (FATAL, PRIORITY, ..., DEBUG); </li>
    <li><strong>__TIME__</strong> - Time with hour of day:minute:second; </li>
    <li><strong>__DATE__</strong> - Date with day:month:year; </li>
    <li><strong>__ISO8601__</strong> - ISO 8601 formatted date; </li>
    <li><strong>__CLASS__</strong> - Class where the message originated; </li>
    <li><strong>__METHOD__</strong> - Method where the message originated;  </li>
    <li><strong>__SOURCE__</strong> - Source file where the message originated;  </li>
    <li><strong>__LINE_NUM__</strong> - Line number where the message originated;</li>
    <li><strong>__TID__</strong> - Thread id where the message originated. </li>
</ul>
The default format of logging messages is used for those levels 
which do not provide their own logging format.
]]>
</property>

<property name="FATAL_Log_Format" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="[__LEVEL__] - [__ISO8601__] - __MESSAGE__"
		  format="&lt;Format String&gt;"
		  default="Default_Log_Format">
Fatal log format specific to fatal log messages.
</property>

<property name="PRIORITY_Log_Format" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="[__LEVEL__] - [__ISO8601__] - __MESSAGE__"
		  format="&lt;Format String&gt;"
		  default="Default_Log_Format">
Priority log format specific to priority log messages.
</property>

<property name="ERROR_Log_Format" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="[__LEVEL__] - [__ISO8601__] - __MESSAGE__"
		  format="&lt;Format String&gt;"
		  default="Default_Log_Format">
Error log format specific to error log messages.
</property>

<property name="WARN_Log_Format" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="[__LEVEL__] - [__ISO8601__] - __MESSAGE__"
		  format="&lt;Format String&gt;"
		  default="Default_Log_Format">
Warn log format specific to warn log messages.
</property>

<property name="INFO_Log_Format" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="[__LEVEL__] - [__ISO8601__] - __MESSAGE__"
		  format="&lt;Format String&gt;"
		  default="Default_Log_Format">
Info log format specific to info log messages.
</property>

<property name="DEBUG_Log_Format" 
          stanza="Logging" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="[__LEVEL__] - [__ISO8601__] - __MESSAGE__"
		  format="&lt;Format String&gt;"
		  default="Default_Log_Format">
Debug log format specific to debug log messages.
</property>

<!-- 
################################################################################
## File: primitive.properties                                                 ##
################################################################################
-->
<property name="Package_Prefixes" 
          stanza="Primitive Control" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="au.edu.labshare.rigclient.primitive;au.edu.rmit.labshare"
		  format="&lt;Package&gt;;...;&lt;Package&gt;"
		  default="">
<![CDATA[
The list of package names that are used in primitive controller class resolution.
Class resolution works using the following algorithm:
<ol>
	<li>The specified controller class name is assumed to be a fully qualified 
	class name and an attempt is made to load it. If it is found then that class
	is used;</li>
	<li>The specified controller class name is appended to the first configured 
	primitive package and an attempt is made to load it. If it is found then that 
	class is used; </li>
	<li>The specified controller class name is appended to the next configured 
	primitive package and an attempt is made to load it. If it is found then 
	that class is used. This occurs until either the class is found or 
	all the configured primitive packages are tried;</li>
</ol>
Multiple primitive package prefixes can be configured using the ';' character as
the delimiter between packages.
]]>
</property>

<!-- 
################################################################################
## File: batch.properties                                                    ##
################################################################################
-->
<property name="Batch_Download_Dir" 
          stanza="Batch Control" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="/tmp"
		  format="&lt;Path&gt;"
		  default="System temp directory">
Directory where batch control uploaded instruction files are stored. If this
is left blank, the system default temporary directory is used. 
</property>

<property name="Batch_Timeout" 
          stanza="Batch Control" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="INTEGER" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="30"
		  format="&lt;int&gt;"
		  default="60">
Batch time out in seconds. Time to wait at batch startup before failing 
batch control, if the batch process has not started. The default is 60
seconds.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Termination_TimeOut" 
          stanza="Batch Control" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="INTEGER" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="5"
		  format="&lt;int&gt;"
		  default="10">
Batch termination time out in seconds. Time to wait before returning a 
batch termination success or failure result.  The default is 10 seconds.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Working_Dir" 
          stanza="Batch Control" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="/var/cache/rigclient"
		  format="[&lt;Path&gt;|null]"
		  default="System temp directory">
Batch process working directory. If this is is set to null, the working
directory is taken to be the System temporary directory. The default is
null.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Create_Nested_Dir" 
          stanza="Batch Control" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="BOOLEAN" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="[true|false]"
		  default="true">
Whether to create a nested working directory per batch control invocation.
If this is set to true, a new directory is created in the batch working
directory and the batch processes working directory is set as the new 
directory. The default is true.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Clean_Up" 
          stanza="Batch Control" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="BOOLEAN" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="[true|false]"
		  default="false">
Whether to run batch clean up. If this is set to true, the batch control 
invocation generated files are deleted. This setting is only honoured if the
property Batch_Create_Nester_Dir property is set to true. If not, it is 
ignored and no clean up run. The default is false.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Flush_Env" 
          stanza="Batch Control" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="BOOLEAN" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="[true|false]"
		  default="false">
Specifies if the batch process should inherit the environment variables of the 
rig client process (the diagnostics page shows the rig client environment 
variables). If true, no inherited environment variables will be given to the
batch process unless they are set up manually. The default value is false.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Instruct_File_Delete" 
          stanza="Batch Control" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="BOOLEAN" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="[true|false]"
		  default="true">
Specifies if the uploaded instruction should be deleted upon completion of 
batch execution. If true, the uploaded batch instruction file is deleted.
The default value is true.
</property>

<!-- ConfiguredBatchRunner properties. -->
<property name="Batch_Exec" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="/bin/false"
		  format="&lt;String&gt;"
		  default="System temp directory">
The batch executable to run. This should be an absolute reference to 
the batch executable that should be invoked for batch control 
(i.e. '/bin/ls' instead of 'ls').
</property>

<property name="Batch_Exec_Arg_1" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="__FILE__"
		  format="[&lt;String&gt;|&lt;Macro&gt;]"
		  default="">
Arguments to provide to the batch executable in order of 1 to n. As many
arguments as needed may be configured provided they follow the format
'Exec_Arg_&lt;Integer&gt;'. The Exec_Arg_ integers must be correctly sequenced,
missing a number will cause subsequent argument configuration to not be
loaded. The arguments are provided to the batch command in the order they
are sequenced. Macros may be used as values. To provide the file as
a command line argument use the __FILE__ macro.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Env_1" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="key:value"
		  format="&lt;String&gt;:[&lt;String&gt;|&lt;Macro&gt;]"
		  default="">
Environment variables to provide for the batch executable process. As may
environment variables as needed may be configured provided they follow
the format 'Env_&lt;Integer&gt;' with the configuration value as environment 
'&lt;Key&gt;:&lt;Value&gt;'. The Env integers must be correctly sequenced, missing a 
number will cause subsequent environment variable configuration to not be
loaded. Macros be use using as the value portion of the environment variable.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Test_File_Extension" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="BOOLEAN" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="[true|false]"
		  default="false">
Whether to test the instruction file extension. If this is set to true,
File_Extension property must be set. The default value is false to specify
not to test a file extension.
</property>

<property name="Batch_File_Extension" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="tar.gz"
		  format="&lt;String&gt;"
		  default="">
Instruction file extension. Should be configured as a string specifying the
characters of the file extension. The file extension test will check if the 
instruction file name ends with the configured extension.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Test_Max_File_Size" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="BOOLEAN" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="[true|false]"
		  default="false">
Whether to test for instruction file maximum size. If this is set to true,
the File_Size property must be set with the maximum permissible instruction
file size. The default value is false to specify not to test for file 
size.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Max_File_Size" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="INTEGER" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="&lt;int&gt;"
		  default="">
Maximum file size of the instruction file in kilobytes.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Test_Magic_Number" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="BOOLEAN" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="[true|false]"
		  default="false">
Whether to test the instruction file for magic number. Many files have constants
that identify the contained data. Detecting such constants in files is an effective 
way of distinguishing between many file formats. If this is set top true, the 
File_Magic_Number property must be set with a hexadecimal representation of the
file magic number. The default value is false to specify not to test for file
magic number.
</property>

<property name="Batch_File_Magic_Number" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="0xCAFEBABE"
		  format="&lt;hex&gt;"
		  default="">
File magic number in hexadecimal format. The prefix '0x' is optional.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Sync_Results_Dir" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="BOOLEAN" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="[true|false]"
		  default="false">
Whether to synchronise the results directory (batch process working directory
to the another directory. If true, the results directory is copied to a
different directory. If true the Sync_Dir_Destination property and 
the Sync_Dir_Name property must be set with the results destination path name
and result directory name respectively. The default is false.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Sync_Dir_Destination" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="/var/rigclient/__YEAR__/"
		  format="&lt;path&gt;"
		  default="">
The absolute path name to the directory to store the results file
directory. Macro variables may be used as path elements. This 
directory must exist for storing results to succeed.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Sync_Dir_Name" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="__USER__"
		  format="&lt;String&gt;"
		  default="">
The name of either the results directory or results file depending on the 
Compress_Dir setting. If Compress_Dir is true, this is used as the file 
name and a suitable file extension is appended to the name.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Compress_Dir" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="BOOLEAN" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="true"
		  format="[true|false]"
		  default="false">
Whether to compress the results directory into a zip archive. The default
false to not compress the results directory.
</property>

<property name="Batch_Compression_Level" 
          stanza="Configured Batch" 
          mandatory="no" 
          type="STRING" 
          restart="yes"
		  example="BEST"
		  format="[BEST|DEFAULT|FASTEST]"
		  default="DEFAULT">
The compression level of the results file. This may be one of the following
compression levels:
<![CDATA[
<ul>
  <li>BEST - Best compression</li>
  <li>DEFAULT - Default compression</li>
  <li>FASTEST - Fastest compression</li>
</ul>
The default compression level is 'DEFAULT'.
]]>
</property>

</config>
